hey spinster society it's sadia sanders
of urbansponsor.com
where we are creating our own agenda
dispelling societal myths and
redefining the word spinster well i am
coming
back with a another product review
before i get into it make sure you are
subscribing to the channel
like and share this video and i want to
acknowledge
my latest subscribers to urban spencer
which are james murphy shantae
raquel anderson lauren blanton
and charlize matthews thank you for
subscribing i hope you're enjoying the
content
let me know if there's something else
you would like me to review
or if you just have a question in
general on this or any other
of my videos okay so let's get into it
this product thera tears eye nutrition i
love this product i have been using it
for many years
it was um i won't say subscribe
prescribed subscribe prescribed because
it's over the counter
but my ophthalmologist which deals with
your eye
health and not just your contacts and
glasses like optometrist she recommended
this product and actually sold it
in her office but i found it at cvs
because i'm always trying to find
a lace a less expensive way to get what
i need
these are about 19.99 at your local cvs
in the box because this comes inside of
a paper box
found in the eye nutrition or eye care
area of your local
pharmacy and that's you know where they
have the the drops and
these of course um contact solution
it would be in the same area so
they are capsules and
this is what they look like
can you see the capsule okay so you take
three of them
every day you don't have to eat first
but if you have a sensitive stomach
maybe you would want to
put something on your stomach beforehand
i take all three of mine at one time
just pop them in so i don't forget
to take them throughout the day and let
me fix this camera because
it is acting stupid okay so
they are basically omega-3 it has some
flaxseed oil
fish oil which is what omega-3 is
uh let's see total calories are 30 total
fat 3 grams of fat
vitamin e and has epa dha i don't even
know what the hell that is
okay but your total omega-3 content is
1200 milligrams
and one serving is three capsules
you get about 30 servings
of three in this bottle because there
are 90
in each one they don't make them any
larger than this that i'm aware of
and also to save money if you have flex
spending account
through your job then what the flex
spending account is
is you are basically trying to budget
your out-of-pocket expenses
for the year sometimes your company
might use calendar year or they might
use
fiscal year fiscal year is july 1st
through june 30th of the following year
or they might use you know january
through december
just depends on your company but you
basically say
uh i think i want to spend maybe a
thousand dollars
this whole year on out of pocket costs
like your co-pays at your doctor's
visits
buying these your sanitary supplies
what you can purchase with the flex
spending account
is always driven by a government
regulation
but you can buy these with your flex
spending account and the purpose of that
account
is so that is pre-tax dollars coming out
of your check
so that's where your savings come in
because this money that
is being set aside in this separate
account is before
any taxes are taken out of your check
and you decide how much or how little
you want
to have available in that account
for the year and nowadays they're
rolling over
to the next year if you don't use a
certain amount before
it was like if you didn't use that whole
thousand dollars you just lost it
and then you were just asked out and you
know like i said
everything is government regulated as
far as which items that you can purchase
with that
back in the day you can purchase alcohol
not drinking alcohol but rubbing alcohol
cotton balls
stuff like that now they kind of cut
that out but
whoever your um plan is
or your company is that administrates or
administers the flex spending
account they'll give you specifics on
what you can buy but this is definitely
something
that you can use with that 19.99 there
are always coupons in the box
just open a box take your coupon
and use it when you check out okay now
dry eye if your contact wear if you
are on the computer all day every day
you're on your phone
all day every day your eyes are going to
get dry
so this alleviates the dry eye without
you having to use drops
i had to have my drops everywhere i went
i could not go
anywhere you know ladies we change
purses
when we're at certain events
concerts i'm like that you don't want a
big old bag you might want to like your
cute little um
what do they call those purses clutch
and then you got to make sure you put
your drops in there i had to
with this i don't have to worry about
getting through the night
in my eyes being just so irritated
this this this this this works i'm
telling you
when i don't take it i feel it and
that's what reminds me
oh crap i didn't take my dear tears now
i'm trying to think how long
it would take before you start feeling
it
um really right away i'd say maybe
a couple of days and that's actually two
days of taking three pills a day so
that's six capsules
you should feel the difference and when
you forget you're gonna feel the
difference because your eyes are gonna
start getting dry again
okay so that's pretty much it make sure
you
you get these use your flex spending
account at work
if you have one open the box get the
coupon out
use that dollar cvs always has good
deals too they usually have like a buy
one get one free
deal going on not all the time but
sometimes they do
so definitely check cvs first um
walgreens
i think walgreens carries them as well
but i found them
at cvs all the time
and if they're out of course you just
ask a manager um
when they're going to be back in stock
or ask them to
order more okay so i want to comment
really quick on my hair i just got my
hair done
this evening and i'm still using the
phyto phyto-specific relaxer
you can go watch that video to hear more
about that it is
a natural they're called a natural
relaxer because it has more plant-based
items in it so it's not as harsh on the
scalp
i got to the point where my scalp would
burn and i didn't have to do anything i
didn't have to scratch it
brush anything i was going to burn this
relaxer has been the only one i've used
in my whole life
and i've been getting relaxers forever
that did not burn
i even took a break from molasses for
about two years
um and had my hair like shaved down here
and kind of long
and and pressed out at the top but this
relaxer works i just got a
little touch up just like around the
edges i guess the sides and the back and
a little in the front
and you see how straight it is so you're
still getting
it straight but it's not uh as harsh of
a chemical
if that makes sense all right and i buy
it online
phyto specific or fido.com but the the
brand is vital specific they have an
index one and index two index two is for
thicker hair that's what i use
fine hair is index one and i had a hard
time finding it in
ulta beauty for the longest time they
were to have like one box left or
then it got to the point where they
didn't have any and i think that's only
because they have changed the
packaging i've noticed but i just get it
online and i take it to my stylist
and let her do it she doesn't order it
because it's kind of expensive
and they don't sell it in those tubs
that most other relaxer brands
allow for stylist purposes because they
have a lot of clients
this is in that one box it's expensive
go watch the other video look at the
comments it's expensive
but it works for me so i'm gonna keep
using it
all right so that's it um let me know
what you think about their tears if
you're using it how it's working for you
if you're not using it
when you go in and purchase it how it
works out for you
again it saves money kind of in the long
run because you're not
buying drops i've had the same bottle of
drops
for a couple of years now i was going
through drops like
you know every month or so i was having
to buy another bottle of drops
don't have to do it now with this been
using it for years
all right talk to you soon until next
time
bye